

Profile

Dedicated games programming student with 4 years educational experience in games programming and 6 years of personal experience in game development. I have developed skills in managing multi-disciplined teams, communication skills and software design. Always looking for new skills to learn and committed to providing high quality results.

Education

(Expected) 2:1 Computer Games Technology, University of Abertay Dundee, Dundee

September 2019 — May 2022

Notable Grades Achieved:

- CMP418 Programming Animation Systems: A+
- CMP303 Network Systems for Game Development: A+
- CMP105 Game Programming: A+
- CMP301 Graphics Programming with Shaders: A
- CMP201 Data Structures and Algorithms 1: A
- CMP202 -Data Structures and Algorithms 2: A
- CMP305 Procedural Methods: A
- MAT301 Mathematics and Artificial Intelligence, Unit 1: A

Employment History

Customer Assistant at Tesco PLC, Dundee

June 2022 — October 2022

Provided a safe shopping experience, ensuring stock was up to date and to code, as well as assisted disabled customers complete their weekly shop and developed relationships with regular customers.

Skills developed as a customer assistant at Tesco include;

- Customer Service
- Assisted Disabled Customers
- Communication

Online Shopper at Sainsburys PLC, Dundee

October 2018 — June 2021

Picked food items in addition to general home products requested by customers through the online shopping system. Some skills developed included;

- · Identifying best quality products
- Adjusted stress in high demanding situations
- Worked cooperatively to fulfil orders on time
- Processing online orders
- Assisted drivers delivering orders to the customers.

Details

Edinburgh Scotland 07795422756 purplemoonone@gmail.com

Links

Portfolio Website DARE Academy Professional Project LinkedIn Profile

Skills

Programming C++, C# and HLSL

DirectX 11 & 12

Data Structures and Algorithms

Animation Systems

Applied Mathematics

OpenGL 4.6

Debugging; PIX, NSight and Render Docs

Communication Skills

Team Management

Blender

Hobbies

Learning French
Personal Game Engine
3D Modelling
Game Jams
Cooking
Walking
Films

Languages

English - C2 (Native)

French - A2

General Assistant at Sainsburys PLC, Edinburgh

October 2016 — July 2017

Developed fundamental skills in assisting customers with queries including;

- · locating items on the shop floor
- · Reducing product pricing
- · Identifying poor product quality or shelf life
- · Working with team members efficiently
- Ensured customer's overall safety and well being within the store

Extra-curricular activities

DARE Academy at SnakeBride Software, Dundee

June 2022 — September 2022

During the summer of 2022, I participated in the Abertay University DARE Academy game development competition, joining SnakeBride Software as a general programmer/producer and helped the team reach the finals.

As a general programmer, I helped produce;

- Procedural Clouds, Particle Systems, animated and shaded foliage
- Volumetric Lighting and Fog
- · Intractable Water Shader

My tasks as a producer included;

- Breaking problems into manageable sub-tasks
- Holding 10-15 minute stand up meetings
- Ensuring everyone on the team were happy and in the development loop

Treasurer at Abertay Game Development Society, Dundee

September 2019 — May 2020

As the treasurer of Abertay's Game Development Society, my responsibility extended beyond maintaining the society's budget and included;

- Ensuring students health and safety during game jam events.
- Volunteering at the Global Game Jam of 2020.
- In addition, my role involved securing guest speakers such as Ninja Kiwi's Executive Vice President, David Hamilton.

★ Additional Skills

Professional Project, Dundee

January 2022 — May 2022

The professional project is a core milestone in the game development courses at the University of Abertay Dundee.

Skills I developed during this time include;

 Organising individual's tasks and identify bottlenecks in the development process.

- Ensuring team members understood agreed upon goals for the week and made sure everyone was listened to
- It was imperative to ensure estimations on complex tasks where procured appropriately and realistically.

◄ References

Gareth Robinson from Abertay University Dundee

g.robinson@abertay.ac.uk · 8235